你好，你们这些漂亮的人。
Hello you beautiful people.
在这段视频中，我们将结束有关如何导航Linux文件系统的讨论
And in this video we're going to be wrapping up our discussion of how to navigate the Linux file system
使用命令行。
using the command line.
在本视频中，您将了解如何使用制表符自动完成来加快导航速度
And in this video you're going to learn how to use tab auto completion to speed up your navigation of
文件系统。
the file system.
我们还将回顾一下我们所学到的所有关于导航错误和
And we're also going to have a recap of what everything that we've learned about navigating falses and
在过去的几个视频中。
in the past few videos.
在本视频结束时，您可以掌握在错误系统中导航所需的所有知识
And by the end of this video you can have all the knowledge that you need to navigate the false system
像个专业人士一样。
like a pro.
只要增加练习，你就会在我们的课程中学到很多东西。
Just add practice and you're going to get plenty of that as we go through the course.
因此，要获取有关制表符自动完成的最后几条信息。
So to get the final few pieces of information about tab auto completion.
让我们直接跳进去吧。
Let's go ahead and jump right into it.
好的。
OK.
因此，让我们继续学习一个非常棒的功能，称为制表符补全。
So let's go ahead and learn about a really awesome feature known as tab completion.
现在，我们当前位于主目录中，您可以通过查看shell提示符看到
Now at the minute we're currently in our home directory as you can see by looking at the shell prompt
另外，通过使用P.W.DICOM，我们可以看到我们在自己的主目录中。
and also by using the P.W. DICOM and we see that we're in our home directory.
现在，我们只需输入cd，然后输入cd，实际上可以跳转到系统的基本目录
Now we could actually jump all the way to the base directory of the system by just typing CD and then
一杯劈开。
a slash.
如果我这样做，您会看到，如果我们使用打印工作目录命令，我们可以看到
And if I do that you'll see that if we use the print working directory command we can see that we are
在我们系统的直接基础上。
in the base direct of our system.
我不想这样做只是为了强调您在使用时不必逐个文件夹地查看
I don't want to do this just to highlight that you don't have to go folder by folder when you using
Siddiq，你实际上可以在你的系统中跳过所有的路。
the Siddiq and you can actually just jump all the way around your system.
所以，举个例子，如果我想一直跳到我的桌面，我不需要先去CD，然后去劈开。
So for example if I wanted to jump all the way to my desktop I don't have to go CD then slash.
你知道我不需要一步一步走完。
You know I don't have to go step by step all the way through.
我可以说CD，把Tilda给它，然后说因为那是我的主文件夹，然后说桌面。
I can just say CD give it the tilda and then say because that's my home folder and then say desktop.
好的。
OK.
现在我们在桌面上，所以你可以看到我们跳来跳去。
Now we are we end up in the desktop so you can you see come into jump around.
你不必一步一步地走。
You don't have to go step by step.
好的。
OK.
很明显，尖叫声是让我们继续，现在了解制表符补全。
So clearly the scream Let's go ahead and now learn about tab completion.
因此，假设我们希望使用绝对路径一直到达我的主目录。
So let's say that we wanted to get all the way to my home directory using an absolute path.
好的。
OK.
我们只需键入就可以做到这一点好的，我们可以键入CD劈开主页劈开Zyad，你知道的
We can do that simply by just typing it all right we can type CDs slash home slash Zyad And you know
如果我们要转到文档，我们可以键入劈开文档。
if we're to go to documents we can type slash documents.
你知道我们会去的。
You know we would be there.
好的，我们会一直到Documents文件夹。
OK we would get all the way to the documents folder.
但是打字需要一点时间。
But typing it takes a bit of time.
它很容易出错，而且您知道我们作为程序员有点懒惰。
It's error prone and you know we're kind of lazy as programmers.
好的，我们想要速度，我们想让事情没有错误，我们希望事情一开始就能正常工作
OK so we want speed and we want things to be without errors and we want things to work right the first
时间到了。
time.
这就是制表符补全的用武之地。
So that's where tab completion comes in.
让我们回到我们的家或回到最基本的目录并清除屏幕。
Let's head back to our home or back to the very base directory and clear the screen.
彼得·比蒂我们在基本目录里。
Peter Beattie we're in the base directory.
这就是您可以使用制表符补全来获得该房间的方法。
This is how you can use tab completion to get that room.
我们想转到Documents文件夹。
We want to get to the documents folder.
好的。
OK.
所以它会是这样的。
So that's going to be like this.
好的，这就是我们要去的地方。
OK that's where we're trying to get to.
让我们看看怎样才能做到这一点，我有CD，可以劈开，这是在家里发生的。
So let's see how we would get there which I've CD can slash now is that it's happening at home.
我们只需键入该页面并按下制表符，您就会看到shell自动完成
We could just type that page and press the tab and you'll see that the shell automatically completed
给我们看那段文字。
that piece of text for us.
这真是太酷了。
Now that's pretty cool.
他们试图输入Ziyad，所以我们只需输入Zed，然后按Tab键，它就会填满我的名字。
They're trying to type out Ziyad So we just type Zed and then we press tab and it's filled out my name.
太棒了，对。
Awesome right.
现在让我们假设我们想要进入文档。
Now let's say we want to go into documents.
好的，我们试试吧。
OK let's let's try it.
大写D，然后按Tab键。
Capital D and press tab.
现在为什么它不起作用了。
Now why is it not working.
我们再试一次。
Let's try again.
电缆不工作。
Cable is not working.
原因是这个大写的D可以指我们主文件夹中的很多东西。
Well the reason is this capital D could refer to lots of things in our home folder.
那么我们来看一看。
So let's take a look at it.
如果我们转到这里的主文件夹。
If we go to our home folder here.
单击屏幕并查看，您可以看到大写D可以指桌面
Click the screen and take a look you can see that the capital D could refer to the desktop it could
请参考下载，也可以参考文档和我们需要的文档。
refer to the downloads or it could refer to the documents and the documents that we want.
好的。
OK.
所以如果一个文件如果你。
So if a file if you.
现在，如果我说好的，我想去大写的D这里，每个经过的人都按两次TAP，它不会
Now if I say OK I want to go to the capital D here and press tap twice with each passing ones it won't
工作。
work.
非常迅速地压制它两次。
Suppress it twice really quickly.
简单得不得了。
Just like that.
实际上它会的。
It will actually.
太多了。
It's a lot.
它实际上会清除屏幕。
It will actually clear the screen.
它会按两次，实际上会告诉我们哪一个匹配。
It will press it twice it will actually tell us which ones it matches.
好的。
OK.
因此，如果我键入doc，我们要进入Documents。
So we want to go into documents if I type doc.
好的。
OK.
因为什么音频和双击还是不好，因为它可以用于文档或下载
Because what audio and double tap that's still no good because it could go for documents or downloads
类型为doc，然后按Tab键。
of a type doc and then press tab.
现在，它将进入文件。
Now it's going to go to documents.
好的。
OK.
我们都在文档文件夹里。
And there we all were in the Documents folder.
所以这太棒了。
So that's awesome.
它极大地降低了我们的打字水平和错误倾向，所以如果我们一直回到
And it cut down our level of typing and error proneness massively So if we go all the way back to the
根目录。
root directory.
现在我们只需输入cd劈开页面标签ZAD标签DOHC标签。
Now we can just type CD slash page tab Zad tab DOHC tab.
我们现在在Documents文件夹中。
There we are in the documents folder.
这真的真的很酷。
It's really really cool.
这将适用于文件名，就像它适用于文件夹一样，非常棒，我一直都在使用它。
This will work for filenames just like it will for folders and it's amazing and I use it all the time.
好的。
OK.
最后一个绝妙的把戏。
Nas one final awesome trick.
让我们不要忘了用图形化的方式去桌面。
Let's not forget to the desktop the graphical way.
好的。
OK.
所以我们要开张了。
So we're going to open.
我们要去黏糊糊的地方。
We're going to go into the gooey.
我们要到桌面，它实际上打开了一个航站楼。
We're going to get to the desk top and it's actually open a terminal.
所以外壳程序是从这个目录中运行的。
So the shell is operating from in this directory.
您可以右键单击，您会注意到这里有一个选项，上面写着“在终端中打开”。
You can right click and you'll notice that you'll see an option here that says Open in terminal.
好的。
OK.
因此，如果我们单击它，您可以看到我们有一个在桌面中自动打开的终端。
So if we click that you can see that we've got a terminal that's automatically opened in the desktop.
例如，假设您正在导航文件、数据、或文档中执行操作
So say for example you're doing stuff in your navigating files in your data in your or your documents
文件夹。
folder.
好的，我们这里有一些文件，比方说。
OK we've got some files in here let's say.
然后，您实际上只需右键单击，然后单击在终端中打开，您现在就可以直接在中操作
Then you could actually just right click and click Open in terminal and you directly now operating in
你的终点站。
your terminal.
从该Documents文件夹中。
From within that documents folder.
因此您知道，如果您正在以图形方式进行操作，然后您想要切换终端，然后切换
So you know if you're doing stuff graphically and then you want to switch the terminal and then switch
这是一个可以使用OK的很好的快捷方式，所以您已经在
back and this is a nice shortcut to be able to use OK so you've learned a whole bunch of stuff in the
最后三个左右关于导航Linux文件系统的视频，所以我只想花点时间
last three videos or so about navigating the Linux file system so I just wanted to take a bit of time
快速回顾一下我们所学的知识，以确保它们都被牢牢记住。
to have a quick recap of what we have learned to make sure that it's all sunk in.
因此，您知道您使用pwt命令来打印shell正在操作的当前工作目录
So you know that you use the PWT command to print the current working directory that the shell is operating
中，它将打印一个绝对路径，指向您的shell当前在文件系统上运行的位置。
in and it will print an absolute path to where on the file system your shell is currently operating.
当您在该目录中时，您可以使用ls命令来查看您周围的内容它是一个列表，因此
You can use the ls command to see what's around you when you are in that directory it is a list so the
目录文件夹的内容是蓝色的，文件是白色的，但是您可以更容易地
contents of the directory folders are in blue and files are in white but you can make that easier to
请参阅使用大写f选项。
see using the the capital f option.
我们还介绍了ls命令可以让您了解查看内容的其他几个选项
And we went through several other options that the ls command can have to make you know viewing things
以及在命令行中查看中的文件。
and viewing files in the in the command line.
容易多了。
A lot easier.
您看到了cd命令可用于更改目录或移动到文件系统上的新位置。
You saw that the cd command can be used to change directory or move to a new location on the file system.
您可以看到，绝对路径是从文件系统的最基本目录开始的路径，因此
And you saw the absolute paths are paths that start at the very base directory of the file system so
劈开和相对路径是从外壳程序当前所在目录开始的路径
the slash and relative paths are the paths that start from the directory that your shell is currently
在……里面。
in.
因此，相对路径通常更容易键入，但绝对路径的结束位置非常清楚
So relative paths are usually easier to type but absolute paths are very clear as to where they end
向上。
up.
好的。
OK.
现在每个目录都有点和点。
Now every directory has the dot and dot dot.
您可以使用ls命令和选项以及圆点1等于4看到的隐藏文件夹
Hidden folders that you can see using the ls command with the option and the dot the one dot is four
表示当前文件夹和两个点Riffe指的是您当前所在的父文件夹。
means the current folder and the two dots Riffe refer to the parent folder of where you currently are.
所以如果你做了CD，然后做了点，这会把你向上移动一个文件夹，好的，因为它是说向上，向上，开始
So if you did CD and then did dot dot that would move you up a folder OK because it's saying Go up go
到我当前所在的父文件夹，如果您确实看到了数据，那么基本上
to the parent folder where I currently am and if you did see the data then that would just basically
把你留在你不会有什么不同的地方。
keep you where you wouldn't make any difference.
好的。
OK.
现在，我们在这段视频中看到了制表符自动完成功能，并且我们看到了tabbouleh委托是非常有用的
Now tab auto completion we saw in this video and we saw that tabbouleh commission is a really useful
加快打字速度并避免错误的技术。
technique to speed up typing and avoiding errors.
如果您按Tab键，什么也没有发生，只需非常迅速地按Tab键两次，它就会向您显示几个
And if you press tab and nothing happens just hit tab twice really quickly and it will show you several
冲突的选项，然后您可以多键入一点以确保它选择
options that are conflicting and you can just then type out a bit more to make sure that it selects
你想要的那个。
the one you want.
就像我们在打印时看到的那样，当我们键入大写D时，它不起作用，但如果按Tab键两次
So like we saw when we print when we type the capital D it wasn't working but if it's press tab twice
我们可以看到，它与文档下载和桌面发生了冲突。
we could see that it was clashing with documents downloads and desktop.
然后我们可以修改它们自己的，以确保Tabbel to Complete有效。
And then we could modify their own to make sure tabel to completion worked.
但是您总是使用Tab键顺序完成，它为您节省了大量时间和麻烦。
But you use tab order completion all the time it saves you so much time and so much hassle.
这是这个节目的一个很好的功能，而且它也可以在任何地方使用，而不仅仅是在导航时使用。
It's a great great feature that the show has and it can also be used anywhere not just when navigating.
因此，如果您正在尝试为命令输入参数，并且它是一个文件路径，那么您可以
So if you're if you are you know trying to enter an argument to a command and it's a file path you can
使用制表符自动完成。
use tab auto completion.
这就是为什么它不只是在使用cd或ls或其他任何东西时才能用得上的原因。
There is why it's not just when using CD or ls or whatever it might be you can use it for pretty much
任何命令。
any command.
如果您想在图形导航时打开当前所在的终端，请使用
And if you want to open up a terminal where you currently are when you're navigating graphically using
图形用户界面只需在终端中点击鼠标右键点击[打开]，就会打开一个终端
the graphical user interface just right click and click Open in terminal and a terminal will open up
当前目录与您打开该终端时所在的位置完全相同。
with the current directory being exactly where you were when you opened that terminal.
这是一个非常有用的功能，如果您只需要在终端上进行一些快速编辑，
So that's a really useful features why if you just need to make some quick edits on the terminal and
然后再把它关起来，然后继续做你正在做的事情。
then shut it again and get back to doing what you are graphically.
这是一个非常棒的功能。
It's a great great feature.
所以一定要记住这一点。
So make sure you keep hold of that.
我们在最后几个视频里有一大堆东西，现在你应该开始感到舒服了
So we've got a whole bunch of stuff in the last few videos and now you should start feeling comfortable
如何导航，只需使用Peter Beattie来查看您所在的位置。
with how to navigate you just use Peter Beattie to see where you are.
LS环顾四周，看看如何移动，在下一个视频中，我们将开始讨论文件扩展名
LS to look around and see to move and in the next video we're going to start discussing file extensions
因为它们不能像在其他操作系统上那样工作，而且有相当多
in Linux because they don't work like they might do on other operating systems and there's quite a few
核心自由属于您在Linux中工作时拥有的扩展。
core freedoms that fall extensions that you have when working in Linux.
所以出于好意，我会在下一个视频中见到你。
So for that goodness I'll see you in the next video.